yspages.com 2017-12-28

# Privacy Policy | YourStory.com

You consent to the use of your personal information by YourStory.com and/or its third party providers and distributors in accordance with the terms of and for the purposes set forth in our Privacy Policy. YourStory does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non affiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

[YourStory.com](https://yourstory.com/) provides the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with YourStory under extremely strict confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help YourStory communicate with you about offers from YourStory and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

You may choose to give us personal information, such as your name, contact number, address or e-mail id that may be needed, for example, to correspond with you, to participate on the site, forum, contests, use of softwares, articles, white papers or to provide you with a subscription. If you tell us that you do not want us to use this information as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes. We intend to protect the quality and integrity of your personally identifiable information. YourStory may share your information with its business partners who sponsor an event, white paper downloads, contest, or promotion; or who jointly offer a service or feature with [YourStory.com](https://yourstory.com/)

We will make a sincere effort to respond in a timely manner to your requests to correct inaccuracies in your personal information. To correct inaccuracies in your personal information please return the message containing the inaccuracies to the sender email id with details of the correction requested.

We sometimes collect anonymous information from visits to our sites to help us provide better customer service. For example, we keep track of the domains from which people visit and we also measure visitor activity on YourStory web site, but we do so in ways that keep the information anonymous. YourStory or its affiliates or vendors may use this data to analyze trends and statistics and to help us provide better customer service. We maintain the highest levels of confidentiality for this information, our affiliates and vendors follow the same high levels of confidentiality. This anonymous information is used and analyzed only at an aggregate level to help us understand trends and patterns. None of this information is reviewed at an individual level. If you do not want your transaction details used in this manner, you can either disable your cookies or opt-out by sending an email to [editor@yourstory.com](mailto:editor@yourstory.com)

YourStory may, if you so choose, send direct mailers to you at the address given by you. You have the option to ‘opt-out’ of this direct mailer by way of links provided at the bottom of each mailer. We respect your privacy and in the event that you choose to not receive such mailers, we will take all steps to remove you from the list.

We transfer information about you if YourStory is acquired by or merged with another company.

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise required by law.

YourStory reserves the right to use the information to provide the user a more personalized online experience. YourStory provides links to web sites and access to content, products and services from third parties, including users, advertisers, affiliates and sponsors of the Site. You agree that YourStory is not responsible for the availability of, and content provided on, third party web sites. The User is requested to peruse the policies posted by other web sites regarding privacy and other topics before use. YourStory is not responsible for third party content accessible through the Site, including opinions, advice, statements and advertisements, and user shall bear all risks associated with the use of such content. YourStory is not responsible for any loss or damage of any sort user may incur from dealing with any third party.

  * Provide you the services that you have requested.
  * Tell you about exciting offers which we think you will value.
  * Customize the content and advertising that you see on [YourStory.com](https://yourstory.com/)
  * Improve your experience on YourStory.com.
  * As otherwise described to you at the point of collection or with your consent

If you have a technical or general support question, please visit [http://YourStory.com/contact-us/](http://yourstory.com/contact-us/) to reach out to us directly.

If you suspect your YourStory account has been hacked or taken over, please visit [http://YourStory.com/contact-us/](http://yourstory.com/contact-us/)to inform us immediately.
